Guide to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello RG.007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series I: Organizations, 4390
  - Subseries D: Sigma Xi, 4392
    - Lecture – University of New Mexico, 1997 September-October; 5275 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Lecture – SUNY Purchase, 1996 September-October; 5276 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Lecture – Penn State, 1996 - 1997 March; 5277 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Norman J. Field Lecture, 1996 March-October; 5278 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Lecture – East Stroudsburg, PA, 1996 October - 1997 May; 5279 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - The Greenwall Foundation Announcement, 2001; 5280 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - George Bugliarello Prize, 2000-2006; 5281 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - 2010 Bugliarello Prize, 5282 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - 1995 Sigma Xi Forum – Vannevar Bush II, Airlie Center Planning Conference, 1994 September 8-11; 5283 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Bugliarello Prize, 2007 August; 5284 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Lectures, 1997 September-October; 5285 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 2010 February; 5286 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Ethics Summit Follow Up – Correspondence, 2010; 5287 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993-1997; 5610 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Executive Director Search Committee – RESTRICT, 1995; 5611 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Subseries E: Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Knowledge Parks Study, 2419
    - Association of University Research Parks AURP – Eco Development Article – "Using Technology to Enhance the Economic Efficiency of Small Retail Establishments", 2007 January – June; 2420 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Bodegas, Summer 2007, 2005-2007; 2421 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Lehman College, 2001 September; 2422 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Progress Reports, 2001 July, 2002 February; 2423 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Pause York Project, 2001 November-December; 2424 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - David Freed – CUNY, 2001 August-December; 2425 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Robert Meeder (Pittsburgh Gateways Corp), Jack Rainey (LaGuardia Community College CUNY), 2001 May; 2426 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - "Jamaica Center: A Model of Knowledge-Driven Urban Development," George Bugliarello, 2002 January 4; 2427 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation – New AirTrain Terminal Celebration, 2004 January 14; 2428 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation – Memoranda, Journal advertisement, 2002 May-September, 2004 January-February; 2429 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - "Enhancement of Economic and Social Development in New York: Two Knowledge Park Prospects" – Proposal, October 13, 2000, 2000 September-December; 2430 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Agendas, 2002 January - 2003 January; 2431 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Approved Grant Proposal, 2000 December - 2001 March; 2432 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Alfred Eisenpreis Consulting Agreement, 2001 February, May; 2433 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Congresswoman Nydia Velazquez, 2006 July-October; 2434 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Letterhead, 2001 July; 2435 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Ted Greenwood, 2001 March, October, 2005 February; 2436 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Sara Nerlove – NSF, 2006 August - 2008 October; 2437 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - York Aviation Conference, March 31, 2003, 2002 November - 2003 February; 2438 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - York College Foundation, 2004 July, September; 2439 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Jerry Posman – COO, York College, 2001 May - 2005 December; 2440 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - York College, 2001 October - 2006 January; 2441 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Jamaica Concurrent Commitment Symposium – Planning, 2002 February-March; 2442 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Request for Grant Extension, 2002 December - 2003 October; 2444 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - William B. Shore – Consulting, 1999 December - 2004 August; 2443 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Project Reports, 2002 February, 2004 October; 2445 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Craig Jenks – Airline/Aircraft Projects, 2002 April - 2004 June; 2446 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Industrial & Technology Assistance Corporation, Greater Jamaica Development Corporation, 2002 April - 2003 February; 2447 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Anthony Perl - York College - Aviation Institute Inaugural Conference, 2003 March-April; 2448 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation – Miscellaneous, 2002 June-September; 2449 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - York College – Remanufacturing Program, 2003 October; 2450 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Pete Luxon – Pittsburgh Gateways, 2003 October-December; 2451 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Seung Ho Lee, 2002 June-July; 2452 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - University of Maryland – FDA Building, 2001 November-December; 2453 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Jamaica Center Project- Keyspan Communications, 2002 March-April; 2454 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 October - 2004 September; 2455 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – MetroTech Proposal, 1999 March-August; 5288 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – Visit, 1999 March 17; 5289 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Knowledge Parks – Ted Greenwood, 2000 November, 2005 August-November; 5290 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Knowledge Parks – Progress Reports, 2002 February - 2004 October; 5291 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Knowledge Parks – Progress Report, 2005 June; 5292 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Knowledge Parks – Miscellaneous, 2001 May - 2004 November; 5293 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Knowledge Parks – Miscellaneous, 2005 June-October, Undated; 5294 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Food Safety, 2001 February-May, Undated; 5295 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Inception of Sloan Knowledge Parks Project, 1999 December - 2000 July; 5296 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Knowledge Parks – Jamaica, Queens, 2000 December - 2001 August; 5297 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Knowledge Parks – Jamaica, Queens, 2001 September - 2003May, Undated; 5298 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Knowledge Parks – Proposal Drafts- Summer 2000, 1996, 1999-2000; 5299 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Knowledge Parks – Progress Report, 2005-2006; 5300 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Center for Urban Technology, 1998-1999; 5301 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Knowledge Parks – Margo Wright – Jamaica Symposium, 2002 February, April; 5302 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Subseries F: Urban Securities Initiative, 1999-2007; 2004-2006; 2127
    - Russia, 2002 December - 2003 February; 2459 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Caroline Purdy, Laura Petonito – Demonstration Project, 2006 October; 2460 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - NSF Proposal – University of Delaware – Resiliency of Urban Complexes, 2006 November; 2461 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - IBM Workshop, 2002 October 29; 2462 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Center for Fire Safety Engineering, 2001 June; 2466 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Congressional Black Caucus Education Braintrust 2006 Symposium, 2006 September; 2467 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Multidisciplinary University Research Initiative – 3D Urban Terrain, 2006 August-October; 2468 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Fire Protection Engineering – Sunil Kumar, 2006 August - 2008 January; 2469 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Mechanical Engineering / FDNY Fire Grant, 2007 January; 2470 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Hurricane Katrina – NSF, 2005 September; 2471 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Department of Homeland Security / FDNY, 2006 October - 2008 April; 2472 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Russian Delegation Visit – Correspondence, 2003 June - 2005 February; 2473 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Russian Delegation Visit – Correspondence, 2005 May - 2006 January, Undated; 2474 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Alumni, 2002; 2128 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - ANSER - Homeland Security Initiative, 2004; 2129 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Albany, New York Trip - RPI Meeting, 2004 August; 2130 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Building Codes, 2005-2006; 2131 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Conference, 2002 April; 2132 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Conference Proceedings, 2003 March; 2133 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Daniel Doctoroff, 2002 March-May; 2134 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Fire Protection Engineering Degree, 2006; 2135 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Victor Goldsmith, 2003; 2136 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Jerry Hultin, 2005; 2137 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Stuart Klein, 2002; 2138 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Master in Security Studies, 2002 August; 2139 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - MetroTech Alliance for Urban Security, 2003 May; 2140 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - MetroTech Evacuation Project, 2005; 2141 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Edward D. Miller, 2002 April; 2142 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - MIT Center for the Study of High Consequence Even Preparedness and Response, 2005; 2143 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 2002-2003; 2144 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - National Consortium for Information Assurance, 2002; 2145 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - New School Urban Issues, 2005; 2146 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - National Science Foundation - Dennis Wenger, 2005; 2147 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - National Science Foundation - New Orleans - Katrina, 2005; 2148 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - NYSTAR Proposal, 2002; 2149 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - NYSTAR Proposal, 2002, 2004; 2150 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Paula A. Crotty - Verizon, 2002 March-April; 2151 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Polytechnic Courses - Center in Urban Sustainability, 2006, 2009; 2152 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Resilience of Urban Complexes, 2007 May; 2153 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Response to Reviewers – Sloan Proposal, 2002 September; 2154 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - RPI Talk, 2003 November; 2155 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - RPI Visit, 2004 February 27; 2156 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - NYSTAR - Russell W. Bessette, 2002 March - 2004 November; 2157 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - New York State Development Initiative, 2002 April - 2003 July; 2158 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Ruth Daniel Visit, 2004 September - 2005 August; 2159 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Society of Fire Protection Engineers (SFPE), 2002 April; 2160 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - SFPE Course, 2003 June 11; 2161 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Study - MetroTech Project, 2006 February - 2007 March; 2162 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Susan Bauman, 2002 April; 2163 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Terrorism, 1999 January; 2164 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Transportation, 1999 April; 2165 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Transportation Security, 2007 July; 2166 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - USI - Miscellaneous, 2001 December - 2002 October; 2167 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - USI - Miscellaneous, 2003 March - 2006 September, Undated; 2168 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Office of Emergency Management, 2004 June - 2005 June; 2169 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Notes, Undated; 2170 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - University of Delaware, 2005 June; 2171 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Urban Security Digital Library, 2003 March; 5303 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "Waging War" article, 2002 February; 2172 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Security Certificate Program, 2003; 2173 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - University of Delaware Visit - Joanne Nigg, 2005 September 6; 2174 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - University of Delaware Project, 2005 December 9; 2175 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Urban Security Brochures, 2002 May 28; 2176 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - United States Conference of Mayors, 2002 March; 2177 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Urban Security Certificate Program, 2003; 2178 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Vayl Oxford - DHS, 2004 September 16; 2179 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Wilt Associates, 2002 January-August; 2180 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Russia, 2003 April - 2006 November; 2181 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Department of Homeland Security Grant, 2003 April - 2005 February; 2930 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Department of Homeland Security Grant, 2005 March; 2931 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Department of Homeland Security Grant, 2005 April-September; 2932 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Department of Homeland Security Grant, Undated; 2933 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Sloan Foundation Visit, September 18, 2002, 2002 August-September; 5304 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Department of Homeland Security – Proposal, 2005; 5305 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Department of Homeland Security – Proposal, Undated; 5306 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "Engineering the Protection of our Cities" Conference – Polytechnic University – October 7, 2002, 2001 December - 2002 October; 5307 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 December - 2005 November, Undated; 5308 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute – Urban Security Collaboration, 2004 March-May; 5309 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Charles McQueary – Department of Homeland Security, 2003 June-July; 5310 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Sloan Foundation – First Year Grant Report, 2003 December; 5311 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - "Russian Challenges in Countering Urban Terrorism", 2004 September, Undated; 5312 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Sloan Foundation Proposal, 2002 July-August; 5313 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Sloan Foundation Award, 2002 September - 2003 January; 5314 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - "Survey of Window Glass Broken by the Oklahoma City Bomb on April 19, 1995" – Glass Research and Testing Laboratory – Texas Tech University, 1996 March; 5315 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – Miscellaneous, 2002 October - 2006 April; 5316 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – Miscellaneous, 2002 March - 2008 November; 5317 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – Miscellaneous, 2002 August – 2006 March, Undated; 5320 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Ted Greenwood – Program Director, Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 2003 June - 2005 October; 5318 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - N.Y.S.T.A.R. Advisory Council to MetroTech – Meeting, March 11, 2003, 2003 February-March; 5319 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – Annual Progress Report, 2003-2004; 5321 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - R.P.I. Meeting, 2004 May 7; 5322 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "News & Terrorism: Communicating in a Crisis" Fact Sheet, 2004; 5323 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Proposal Drafts, 2002 August 5; 5324 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Urban Security Initiative, 2006 October; 5325 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated; 5326 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Issues of Risk Analysis, Russian Scientific Society for Risk Analysis, 2005-2006; 5327 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - University of Delaware – Resilience Project – 1, Undated; 5328 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - University of Delaware – Resilience Project – 2, Undated; 5329 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - University of Delaware – Resilience Project – 3, Undated; 5330 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - University of Delaware – Resilience Project – 4, Undated; 5331 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - University of Delaware – Resilience Project – 5, Undated; 5332 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Urban Terrain Modeling, 2006 August-October; 5333 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001-2002; Undated; 5334 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - U.S.I. – Promotional Material, Undated; 5335 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence – Miscellaneous, 2002 October, 2004 December; 5336 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 2006; 5337 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Budget, 2000-2002; 5338 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Department of Homeland Security – Center for the Study of Natural Disasters, Coastal Infrastructure and Emergency Management, 2007 February-April; 5339 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - National Security Agency Visit, 2002; 5340 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - United States Army - CECOM Research Development and Engineering Center – 1, 1999-2002; 5341 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - United States Army - CECOM Research Development and Engineering Center – 2, 1999-2002; 5342 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Fire Grant, 2008 January; 5343 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Russian Visit, 2003 January; 5344 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Data, 2007-2008; 5616 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Proposals, 2006-2009; 5617 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Proposals, 2010, Undated; 5618 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Subseries G: Miscellaneous, 5345
    - A.A.A.S. - Advisory committee on International Science Meeting, 2001 September 24; 5346 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - A.A.A.S. - Presidential Candidacy, 2001 December; 5347 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - A.S.C.E. – Correspondence – Congratulating Notes, 2004 November 29; 5348 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science – Election 2001, 5349 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks, 2000 April; 5350 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks, 2005-2008; 5351 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks – 6th Annual Awards of Excellence, 2000; 5352 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks – Awards, 2000 April-June; 5353 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks – Nomination, 2000 April; 5354 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks - Presentation to the Ninth Annual International Conference of the Association of University Related Research Parks, 1994 May 13; 5619 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment – Critical Infrastructure Roundtable, 2005 May - 2006 January; 5355 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Center for the Study of Ethics in the Professions, 2009 September, 2010 March; 5620 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Center for Urban Technology, 1998 June - 1999 August; 5621 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Chinese Academy of Sciences, 2003 October; 5356 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Chinese-America Frontiers of Engineering, 2010 November-December; 5622 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Coleman Foundation, 2005 July; 5623 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - ComTech, 2001 October - 2002 February; 5357 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Council on Academies of Engineering and Technological Sciences – Mexico City, 2011; 5624 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Division Committee on Engineering and Physical Sciences, 2011 January; 5625 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Ferrol Metropoli Foundation, 2004 May - 2006 March; 5358 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Fondazione Internazionale Trieste (FIT), 2006 April-June; 5359 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Foundation for the Future – "The Future: Young Scholar's Inquiry" – Seminar I, Proceedings, 2005 June 9; 5626 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Foundation for the Future – Humanity 3000 Symposium No. 1 Proceedings, Volume I, 2000 August 12-16; 5627 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Foundation for the Future – Humanity 3000 Symposium No. 1 Proceedings, Volume II, 2000 August 12-16; 5628 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation, 2008-2009; 5629 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation - Dr. Ted Greenwood, 2008 June; 5630 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - InTech Project, 2010 November 3; 5360 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - International Association of Science Parks – World conference, 2002 September; 5361 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - International Association of Science Parks – World conference – Galley proof, 2002 September; 5362 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - International Eurasian Academy of Science, 1999 April; 5631 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Invitations and Programs, 1985-1992, Undated; 5632 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Italian Academy of Science, 2005 January-October; 5363 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Italian Ministry, 2002 September; 5633 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Italian Scientists and Scholars in North American Foundation, 2009 April 24; 5364 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Jura Board – Pat Finneran, 2011 February; 5634 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Jura Corporation, 2010 December - 2011 January; 5365 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory – RESTRICT, 1999-2000; 5635 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory Engineering Advisory Committee, 1997 December - 1998 March; 5636 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Lord Foundation – Annual Meeting of Directors, Massachusetts, 2008 April - 2010 May; 5366 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Lord Foundation – Annual Meeting of Directors, North Carolina, 2006 May - 2009 May; 5367 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Lord Foundation – Board of Directors Summer Meetings, 1999-2010; 5368 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Lord Foundation – Strategy Committee Meetings, 2006-2010; 5369 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Lord Foundation – Strategy Committee Meetings, 2008; 5370 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Lord Foundation – Strategy Committee Meeting, 2009 April; 5371 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Lord Foundation – Strategy Committee Meeting, 2010 October-November; 5372 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Lord Foundation of Massachusetts, 2010 August 10; 5373 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Lord Foundation of North Carolina, 2010 June; 5374 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Lord Foundation of North Carolina, 1997 December 15; 5375 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Richard Lounsbery Foundation, 2008 January; 5639 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Marconi Fellowship – Miscellaneous, 1993-2001; 5376 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Marconi Fellowship – Miscellaneous, 2002-2010, Undated; 5377 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Marconi Society International Fellowship At Columbia University – Board Meeting, 2005 November 3; 5378 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Mexican Academy of Engineering Visit, 2009 November 3-4; 5379 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - N.S.F. – Engineering Shortage Data, 1999 June; 5380 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - New York City Accelerator for a Clean & Renewable Economy, 2010 June 15; 5637 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - New York City Housing Partnership, 1992 July; 5381 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - New York City Partnership – Infrastructure Task Force, 1999 February-July; 5382 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - New York City Partnership – Miscellaneous, 1994-2001; 5383 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - New York City Trade Mission – London – Photo Album, 1983 February; 5638 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development, 1991-1996; 5384 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Saint Anthony Falls Laboratory – University of Minnesota, 2006 September – 2007 April; 5642 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Saint Anthony Falls Laboratory – University of Minnesota, 2007 May-November; 5641 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Saint Anthony Falls Laboratory – University of Minnesota – Alumni Spotlight, 2011 January 5; 5640 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Society of Fire Protection Engineers (SFPE), 2007 March; 5643 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Paul & Daisy Soros Fellowships for New Americans, 2000 November 3; 5385 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Paul & Daisy Soros Fellowships for New Americans, 2010 March; 5386 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Paul & Daisy Soros Fellowships for New Americans, 2010 November-December; 5387 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Transportation Research Board, 2009 October-December; 5388 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Transportation Research Board Meeting, 2010 September - 2011 January; 5644 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - UNESCO International Centre for Engineering Education – 5th Global Congress on Engineering Education, 2006 July 17-21; 5645 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - UNESCO Publications and Contracts, 2008-2010; 5646 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Whitaker Foundation - Second Annual Report - "Special Opportunity" Award – "A National Urban Model for Biomedical Engineering Training", 1995 November 30; 5647 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Series II: Subject Files, 2475
  This series contains original subject files kept in George Bugliarello's office (Jacobs Building, Room 350) and containing mostly correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, notes, and clippings.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by folder title. The folders pertaining to the development of MetroTech Center have been separated into their own subseries based on the volume of documents on the topic.
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical Files, 3101
    - 16th International Conference on Mechanics in Medicine and Biology at the University of Pittsburgh – References & Research, 2008; 5389 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - AAAS – Fellows, 2004 November; 2477 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - AAAS – Miscellaneous, 1994 May, 1995 January; 2476 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - AAAS – Poverty Eradication, 2008 September; 2478 (Box 18, Folder 4)